{
    "id": "68019cbcf87042c4b3e1325257af9f9b",
    "title": "Joining two sentences using a relative pronoun",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "71d8b927105045e7ae0298b5930f2765",
            "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He is a cheerful boy ............................................. everybody loves.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is the house .............................................. Jack built.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "what",
                        "who"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is the person ................................................... I want to see.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is the offender ................................................ the police have arrested.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "which",
                        "whom"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "My father, ..................................................... hardly received any formal education, went on to become a great leader.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "that",
                        "whom"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was my teacher .................................................... I will never forget.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is the player ................................................ the committee selected captain.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "That is the road ................................................... leads to the railway station.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "which",
                        "what",
                        "where"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "My uncle, ...................................................... had been ailing for a while, died last week.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "which",
                        "whom"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The car ................................................. was going at over 100 mph dashed against a tree.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "what",
                        "which",
                        "who"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}